Salvador Luria Papers 1923-1992 Mss.Ms.Coll.39
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Works by others, 1944-1990; 11 linear feet
  - A Comparative Study of Bacteriophage P2 in rec+ and rec- Escherichia Coli K-12 Hosts, Jun. 1968; Laffler, Thomas G. (Box 61)
  - Lysogeny of Phage P2 in a rec- Mutant of E. Coli K-12, n.d.; Laffler, Thomas G. (Box 61)
  - The Inheritance of Acquired Characteristics, [1990]; Landman, Otto K. (Box 61)
  - Discussion of Dr. Stanley's Paper, n.d.; Latarjet, Raymond, 1911- (Box 61)
  - Current Concepts of Feedback Inhibition, n.d.; Latham, Harriet (Box 61)
  - Genetic Studies of Lysogenecity in Escherichia Coli, n.d.; Lederberg, Esther; Lederberg, Joshua (Box 61)
  - Mechanism of Action of Penicillin, n.d.; Lederberg, Joshua (Box 61)
  - Simple Method for Isolating Individual Microbes, [195-]; Lederberg, Joshua (Box 61)
  - Genetic Functions of Prophage: Interference with the Multiplication of Heterologous Bacteriophages, 1955; Lederberg, Seymour Samuel (Box 62)
  - On Peptide Chain Initiation, n.d.; Lengyel, Peter (Box 62)
  - Transduction in Strains of E. Coli, n.d.; Lennox, E. S., (Edwin Samuel), 1920- (Box 62)
  - Genetic Studies with Mutants of Phage P22 Affecting Lysogenization of Salmonella Typhimurium--Lecture, [1957]; Levine, Myron (Box 62)
  - Coding Aspects of Protein Synthesis, n.d.; Levinthal, Cyrus (Box 62)
  - Genetic and Chemical Studies with Alkaline Phosphatase of E. Coli, Levinthal, Cyrus (Box 62)
  - The Hereditary Virus of Drosophila, [1957]; L'Hétitier, Ph. (Box 62)
  - Hormones of the Adenohypophysis, n.d.; Li, Choh Hao (Box 62)
  - The Production of Bacteriophage Mutants by a Disturbance of DNA Metabolism, n.d.; Litman, Rose M.; Pardee, Arthur B. (Box 62)
  - Structural Relationships of Salmonella O and R Antigens, 1965; Galanos, C.; Lüderitz, Otto; Risse, H.J. (Box 62)
  - Luria, Zella (Box 62)
    -See Ser.III, The Soluble and
  - Thesis Exam, Oct. 1976; Lusk-Braun, Joan (Box 62)
  - Factors Influencing the Evolution of Viral Diseases at the Cellular Level and in the Organism--Lecture, Lwoff, André, 1902- (Box 62)
  - Nomenclature et Symboles pour la Description des Relations entre Bactéries et Bactériophages, Lwoff, André, 1902- (Box 62)
  - Remarks on the Terminology of Viruses and of Viral Infections, Lwoff, André, 1902- (Box 62)
  - Cell Size and Chemical Composition During Balanced Growth of Salmonella Typhimurium, Kjeldgaard, Niels Ole; Maaløe, Ole; Schaechter, M. (Box 62)
  - The Integration of Protein and RNA Synthesis in Bacteria, Kurland, C.G.; Maaløe, Ole (Box 62)
  - "The Normal DNA Replication Cycle, II", n.d.; Hanawalt, Philip Courtland; Maaløe, Ole (Box 62)
  - Regulation of Ribosomal and Transfer RNA Synthesis, Kurland, C.G.; Maaløe, Ole (Box 62)
  - "Regulation of the Protein Synthesizing Machinery - Ribosomes, tRNA, Factors, etc.", n.d.; Maaløe, Ole (Box 62)
  - Thymine Deficiency and the Normal DNA Replication Cycle, Hanawalt, Philip Courtland; Maaløe, Ole (Box 62)
  - Viet Nam and World Revolution: A Suggestion for Widening and Deepening Debate on the War in Asia, [1966]; Maccoby, Michael (Box 62)
  - Effects of 32P Decay on Enzyme Synthesis, n.d.; McFall, Elizabeth (Box 62)
  - The Effects of Thymine and of Phosphate Deprivation on Enzyme Synthesis in Escherichia Coli, Magasanik, Boris; McFall, Elizabeth (Box 62)
  - The Effects of Thynine Deprivation on the Synthesis of Protein in Escherichia Coli, n.d.; Magasanik, Boris; McFall, Elizabeth (Box 62)
  - The Relation of Enzyme Synthesis to the RNA Level of Normal and of Thymine-Starved Escherichia Coli, Magasanik, Boris; McFall, Elizabeth (Box 62)
  - Evolutionary Trends of the Triune Brain: From Imitation to Creativity--Synopsis, Sep. 1972; MacLean, Paul D. (Box 62)
  - Microscopic Anatomy of the Nervous System--Lecture, n.d.; McMahan, U.J. (Box 62)
  - Gene Regulation from Sites Near and Far, Magasanik, Boris (Box 62)
  - Regulation of Growth and Composition of the Bacterial Cell, Magasanik, Adele K.; Magasanik, Boris; Neidhardt, Frederick C. (Box 62)
  - Conservation and Divergence in the Two Closely Related Colicins Ia and Ib: DNA and Amino Acid Sequence Analysis of Colicin and Immunity Genes, Hsu, Chi-Hsin; Konisky, Jordan; Mankovich, John (Box 62)
  - The Clone Size Distribution of T4rII+ Revertants from Various Bacteriophage Strains in Single Burst Analysis, [1972]; Marcovich, Herbert; Vigier, P.R.R. (Box 63)
  - Bacillus Subtilis DNA Polymerase III Is Required for the Replication of the Virulent Bacteriophage øe, [1974]; Lavi, Uri; Marcus, Menashe; Nattenberg, Alona; Ronen, Amiram (Box 63)
  - Denaturation and Renaturation of Deoxyribonucleic Acid, Marmur, Julius; Rownd, R.; Schildkraut, Carl L. (Box 63)
  - Growth of Heavy Isotope Labeled Bacteria for the Isolation of Nucleic Acids, n.d.; Marmur, Julius; Schildkraut, Carl L. (Box 63)
  - A Procedure for the Isolation of Deoxyribonucleic Acid from Microorganisms, n.d.; Marmur, Julius (Box 63)
  - Man Faces Extinction...Scientists Say Fallout Endangers Human Race, 1961; Marshall, Jonathan (Box 63)
  - Chromosome Breakage Accompanying Genetic Recombination in Bacteriophage, n.d.; Meselson, Matthew; Weigle, Jean J. (Box 63)
  - The Molecular Basis of Genetic Recombination, Sep. 1965; Meselson, Matthew (Box 63)
  - A Molecular Explanation of Lysogeny and Induction of Lambda, Meselson, Matthew (Box 63)
  - Morituri Te Salutamus, [1966]; Mitchell, Kenneth H. (Box 63)
  - On the Nature of Allosteric Transitions: A Plausible Model, 1964; Changeux, Jean-Pierre; Monod, Jacques; Wyman, Jeffries, 1814-1874 (Box 63)
  - Experimental Membranes and Mechanisms of Bioenergy-Transductions, 1976; Montal, M. (Box 63)
  - [Peace through Common Sense], [1966]; Morrison, Philip (Box 63)
  - Fiction and Fact Concerning American Policy in Vietnam, 8 Nov. 1966; Morse, Wayne (Box 63)
  - An Introduction to the Quantitative Analysis of Mammalian Cells in Vitro, Jul. 1958; Moser, Hermann (Box 63)
  - Facteurs de la Sensibilité des Levures à l'Action l'Étale des Radiations Ionisantes. Étude d'un Mutant Radiorésistant, 1964; Moustacchi, Ethel (Box 63)
  - Natural Factors Influencing Host Response, Mar. 1960; Muhlbock, O. and L.M. Boot (Box 63)
  - The Role of Amniocentesis in the Intra-Uterine Detection of Genetic Disorders, n.d.; Gerbie, Albert B.; Nadler, Henry L. (Box 63)
  - Association between Colicinogenic and Fertility Factors, [1966]; Nagel de Zwaig, Rosa (Box 63)
  - Colicinogenic Factors V and I and Bacterial Fertility, Nagel de Zwaig, Rosa (Box 63)
  - Interactions between Colicinogenic Factors B and F Type Factors, [1971]; Nagel de Zwaig, Rosa (Box 63)
  - Mode of Action of Colicin A, n.d.; Nagel de Zwaig, Rosa (Box 63)
  - Cytoplasmic Inheritance, Dec. 1959; Nanney, D.L. (Box 63)
  - Magnesium Transport in Escherichia Coli, 1970; Kennedy, Eugene P.; Nelson, David L. (Box 63)
  - The Release of Ribonuclease into the Medium when E. Coli Cells Are Converted to Spheroplasts, 1964; Neu, H.C. and L.A. Heppel (Box 63)
  - NADP-Specific Glutamate Dehydrogenase Is Not the Repressor of Yeast Sporulation by Ammonia, [1979]; Newlon, Michael C. (Box 63)
  - "Denervation, Reinnervation and the Growth of Neurons--Lecture", 1972; Nicholls, John G. (Box 64)
  - Lecture Notes on Synaptic Transmission, n.d.; Nicholls, John G. (Box 64)
  - Lecture Notes on the Ionic Mechanisms Involved in Neural Signalling, 1971; Nicholls, John G. (Box 64)
  - Muscle Spindles and the Regulation of Muscular Contraction--Lecture, Nicholls, John G. (Box 64)
  - Deletion Mutants of the rouB Gene Cluster in Salmonella Typhimurium, n.d.; Levinthal, Mark; Nikaido, Hiroshi; Nikaido, Kishiko (Box 64)
  - Phospholipid as a Possible Component of Carrier System in Beta-Galactosidase Permease of Escherichia Coli, n.d.; Nikaido, Hiroshi (Box 64)
  - Biological Activity of 5-Hydroxymethyluracil and Its Deoxynucleoside in Noninfected and Phage-Infected Bacillus Subtilis, 1969; Aposhian, H. Vasken; Friedman, Norman; Nishihara, Mutsuko (Box 64)
  - RNA Metabolism in Escherichia Coli Infected with Bacteriophage T4. I. Inhibition of Host Ribosomal and Soluble RNA Synthesis by Phage and Effect of Chloromycetin, Asano, Kimiko; Nomura, Masayasu; Okamoto, Koji (Box 64)
  - "Enzyme Induction, an All or None Phenomenon", 1957; Novick, Aaron; Weiner, Milton (Box 64)
  - The Genetic Basis of Hyper-Synthesis of Beta-Galactosidase, n.d.; Horiuchi, Sumiko; Horiuchi, Tadao; Novick, Aaron (Box 64)
  - Isolation and Properties of Bacteria Capable of High Rates of Beta-Galactosidase Synthesis, Horiuchi, Sumiko; Horiuchi, Tadao; Novick, Aaron (Box 64)
  - Mutagens and Anti-Mutagens, 1955; Novick, Aaron (Box 64)
  - The Non-Inducibility of Repressor Formation, Medved, Joan K.; Novick, Aaron; Sadler, John R. (Box 64)
  - The Properties of Repressor and the Kinetics of Its Action, 1 Nov. 1964; Novick, Aaron; Sadler, John R. (Box 64)
  - A Temperature-Sensitive Regulatory System, n.d.; Horiuchi, Sumiko; Horiuchi, Tadao; Novick, Aaron (Box 64)
  - Functions of a New Photoreceptor Membrane, 1973; Oesterhelt, Dieter; Stoeckenius, Walter (Box 64)
  - Why at Cambridge? Why at Cal Tech?, n.d.; Olby, Robert (Box 64)
  - The Phenotypic Repair of Defective Genotypes in Bacteria by Streptomycin and Other Compounds: Need of Continuity in a DNA Strand for the Transcription of Messages?, Ortega (Box 64)
  - Mutational Analysis of a Yeast Transcriptional Terminator, n.d.; Guarente, Leonard; Osborne, Brian I. (Box 64)
  - The Active Historian: Freedom and Responsibility, [1966]; Osgood, Charles E. (Box 64)
  - The Baited Hook, [1966]; Osgood, Charles E. (Box 64)
  - On the Regulation of DNA Transcription, n.d.; Paigen, Kenneth (Box 64)
  - Evidence for Diffuse Growth of the Cylindrical Portion of the Murein Sacculus Based on the Topography of [3H] Diaminopimelic Acid in Thin Sections of Pulse-Labeled Escherichia Coli, Park, James T.; Raichler, Judith (Box 64)
  - Salmonella Typhi Murium and Phage A.1, Parry, W.R. (Box 64)
  - Reversible Effects of Chaotropic Agents on the Protein Permeability of Escherichia Coli Membrane Vesicles, n.d.; Kaback, H. Ronald; Patel, Lekha; Schuldiner, Shimon (Box 64)
  - "Trespassing"" on the Bomb Site""", Sep. 1957; Peck, James (Box 64)
  - Studies of Deoxyribonucleic Acid Metabolism in Bacteria Infected by Bacteriophage T5, n.d.; Pfefferkorn, Elmer (Box 64)
  - The High Cost of Secrecy to Science, 1-May-56; Piel, Gerard (Box 64)
  - Thioredoxin Catalyzed Refolding of Disulfide-Containing Proteins, n.d.; Pigiet, Vincent P.; Schuster, Barbara J. (Box 64)
  - Active Transport in Colicin K-Insensitive Mutants, n.d.; Plate, Charles A. (Box 64)
  - Colicin K as a Probe of Energy Coupling in Escherichia Coli, n.d.; Plate, Charles A. (Box 64)
  - Effect of Colicin K on Enzyme Induction in Escherichia Coli K12, Clark, Virginia L.; Plate, Charles A.; Suit, Joan L. (Box 64)
  - Effect of Colicin K on the Expression of Catabolite Repressible Operons, n.d.; Plate, Charles A.; Suit, Joan L. (Box 64)
  - Identification of a Proton-Motive Force Related Regulatory System in Escherichia Coli and Its Effects on Lactose Transport, [1985]; Laffler, Thomas G.; Plate, Charles A. (Box 64)
  - A Mutant of Escherichia Coli Defective in Response to Colicin K and in Active Transport, [1975]; Plate, Charles A. (Box 64)
  - A New Class of Energy Uncoupled Mutants of Escherichia Coli, n.d.; Plate, Charles A.; Suit, Joan L. (Box 64)
  - Purification and the Use of Colicins as Probes to Study Energy Transduction in E. Coli and Derived Membrane Vesicles, [1976]; Plate, Charles A. (Box 64)
  - Requirement for a Membrane Potential in the Active Transport of Glutamine by Escherichia Coli, 1978; Plate, Charles A.; Weiss, Michael J. (Box 64)
  - The Structure of the Bacterial Cell Envelope as Related to Colicin Action and Colicin Tolerance, Plate, Charles A. (Box 64)
  - How Men Can Shape Their Future, Oct. 1970; Platt, John (Box 64)
  - Notes on the Exponential Growth of AIDS Disease and Possible Social Effects by 1988, Platt, John (Box 64)
  - A Suggested Classification of Crisis Research Studies by Project Areas, Nov. 1969; Platt, John (Box 64)
  - Protein Code. Work Note 1, n.d.; Platt, (Box 64)
  - The Jubilee Symposium - Roche and the Human Problems of Biomedical Progress, [1971]; Pletscher, Alfred (Box 65)
  - The Harmful Effects of Genetic Radiation, 18 Jun. 1962; Plough, H.H. (Box 65)
  - Microbial Genetics: Retrospect and Prospect, 6 Dec. 1962; Pontecorvo, G. (Box 65)
  - Symbols Inside and Outside of Language, 1973; Premack, David (Box 65)
  - There is No Morality in Nixonism, 1972; Priestino, Donaldo H. (Box 65)
  - Isolation of the L Phage Repressor, n.d.; Ptashne, Mark (Box 65)
  - The L Phage Repressor Binds Specifically to L DNA, Ptashne, Mark (Box 65)
  - Studies on Lysogeny and Conjugation in Escherichia Coli, Jun. 1965; Ptashne, Mark (Box 65)
  - The Mammalian Cells as Micoorganism, Jul. 1956; Puck, Theodore T., (Theodore Thomas), 1916-2005 (Box 65)
  - Tetraparental Mice in the Study of Developmental Biology, Mar. 1977; Raulet, David (Box 65)
  - Suppression of the Heat-Sensitive Mutants of the Coliphage Lambda, 1967; Regös, J. and K. Szende (Box 65)
  - Restriction of Non-Glucosylated T-Even Phages in E. Coli K-12 and B, Kanowith, Susan; Revel, Helen R. (Box 65)
  - A Hybrid Helix Containing Both Deoxyribose and Ribose Polynucleotides and Its Relation to the Transfer of Information between the Nucleic Acids, Rich, Alexander (Box 65)
  - On the Problems of Evolution and Biochemical Information Transfer, Rich, Alexander (Box 65)
  - Genetic Recombination in Escherichia Coli K-12, 1957; Richter, Alan (Box 65)
  - The Occurrence of Beta-Galactosidase in the Genus Shigella, [1959]; Rickenberg, Howard V. (Box 65)
  - [Idealists...Dangerous in War], [1966]; Riesman, David (Box 65)
  - Japanese Attitudes Towards the United States Shelter-Building Program, n.d.; Riesman, David (Box 65)
  - Sedimentation Analysis of DNA Degradation Products Resulting from the Action of Colicin E2 on E. Coli, n.d.; Ringrose, Peter (Box 65)
  - Evidence for an Intermediate Stage in the Biosynthesis of the Salmonella O-Antigen, n.d.; Dankert, M.; Robbins, P.W.; Wright, A. (Box 65)
  - Polysaccharide Biosynthesis, n.d.; Dankert, M.; Robbins, P.W.; Wright, A. (Box 65)
  - The Question of the Direction of Chain Growth in Polysaccharide Synthesis, n.d.; Bray, Dennis; Dankert, M.; Robbins, P.W.; Wright, A. (Box 65)
  - The Shope Papilloma Virus: A Passenger in Man and Its Significance to the Potential Control of the Host Genome, Rogers, Stanfield (Box 65)
  - Relative Depletion of an Argentine-Rich Deoxyribonucleohistone Component During Tumor Induction by the Shope Papilloma Virus, [1967]; Evans, John H.; Rogers, Stanfield (Box 65)
  - An Introduction to the Biological Sciences, n.d.; Roos, Thomas B. (Box 65)
  - A Procedure to Determine the Polarity of the Phosphatase Operon, n.d.; Rosbash, Michael (Box 65)
  - Phenomènes de Recombinaison Intragénique et Unité Fonctionelle d'un Locus Chez l'Ascobolus Immersus, 1964; Rossignol, Jean-Luc (Box 65)
  - Expression of Newly Transferred Genes Controlling Beta-D-Galactosidase Synthesis in Escherichia Coli, 1964; Ganesan, Ann K.; Rotman, Boris (Box 65)
  - Measurement of Activity of Single Molecules of Beta-D-Galactosidase, 1961; Rotman, Boris (Box 65)
  - Transport of Galactose from the Inside to the Outside of Escherichia Coli, 1961; Guzman, Rosario; Rotman, Boris (Box 65)
  - Humoral Immune Response to the Entire HIV Envelope Glycoprotein Made in Insect Cells, [1987]; Lynn, Debra L.; Robert-Guroff, Marjorie; Rusche, James R. (Box 65)
  - Mutants of the Col E1 Plasmid, 1982; Sabik, Joseph F. (Box 65)
  - Proposal for Summer Funding, 1981; Sabik, Joseph F. (Box 65)
  - A Specific Reversible Inhibition of Bacteriophage T2 of Escherichia Coli by Host Cell Fragments, 1952; Sagik, Bernard Phillip (Box 65)
  - Isolation of Bacteriophages by Polyethelene-Glycol-Dextransulfate Two Phase Systems and by PEG Precipitation: Methods of General Applicability, [1967]; Salser, Winston (Box 66)
  - Genetic Analysis of the Suppressor Strains of Shigella and Sh-E. Coli Recombinants, Sarkar, S. (Box 66)
  - Les Réactions Hétérospécifiques dans l'Étude de la Transformation Bactérienne, 1961; Schaeffer, Pierre (Box 66)
  - Comparative Susceptibility of Cells of the Same Type, [1957]; Scherer, William F. (Box 66)
  - Civil Defense, n.d.; Schreiber, William F. (Box 66)
  - Nuclear Weapons Development and OCD's Fallout Shelter Program, Cohen, Robert S.; Schreiber, William F. (Box 66)
  - "Statement to the Committee on Public Safety of the General Court of 1963, the State House, February 14, 1963", 14 Feb. 1963; Schreiber, William F. (Box 66)
  - Isolation of Tolerant Mutants, [1968?]; Schwarz, Terek F.R. (Box 66)
  - Some Aspects of Colicin Tolerance in Escherichia Coli K12, May-72; Schwarz, Terek F.R. (Box 66)
  - The Genetic Code and Human Language, Shanon, Benny (Box 66)
  - An Amber Suppressor tRNA Gene Derived by Site Specific Mutagenesis: Cloning and Function in Mammalian Cells, [1982]; Belagaje, Ramamoorthy; Laski, Frank A.; Rajbhandary, Uttam L.; Sharp, Phillip A. (Box 66)
  - Autoradiographs Relating Nucleic Acid Metabolism to the Appearance of Inracellular Vaccinia Virus, 1961; Sheek, Martha Reyburn (Box 66)
  - On the Relationship between Recombination and Transcription of the Lactose Genes of Escherichia Coli K 12, 1967; Barbour, Stephen D.; Shestakov, Sergey (Box 66)
  - Unidentified, n.d.; Shub, (Box 66)
    See also Ser.VII, Shub
  - Protein Structure and Evolution, 10 Nov. 1965; Siev, Moshe (Box 66)
  - Gene Manipulation: Progress and Prospects, 1971; Signer, Ethan R. (Box 66)
  - Non-Heritable Factors in Gene Expression, Jan. 1963; Signer, Ethan R. (Box 66)
  - Recombination in Phage L: II. Site-Specific Recombination Promoted by the Integration System, n.d.; Signer, Ethan R.; Weil, Jon (Box 67)
  - Site-Specific Recombination in Bacteriophage L, n.d.; Signer, Ethan R.; Weil, Jon (Box 67)
  - Conversion of Beta-Galactosidase to a Membrane-Bound State by Gene Fusion, 1976; Beckwith, Jonathan R.; Casadaban, Malcolm J.; Shuman, Howard A.; Silhavy, Thomas J. (Box 67)
  - Some Biological Problems in Cancer Biochemistry, n.d.; Axelrad, Arthur; Siminovitch, Louis (Box 67)
  - The Nucleic Acids of the Bacterial Viruses, n.d.; Sinsheimer, Robert L. (Box 67)
  - The Nature of the Defect in the Abnormal Bacteriophage T2, 1958; Smith, Sylvia Margaret (Box 67)
  - DOM (STP) a New Hallucinogenic Drug and DOET: Effects of Low Doses in Man, 1968; Faillace, Louis A.; Snyder, Solomon H.; Weingartner, Herbert (Box 67)
  - Effects of Ethidium Bromide on Plasmids in Escherichia Coli K-12, [1970]; Sollner, Barbara (Box 67)
  - The Evolutionary Integration of the Genetic Material into Genetic Systems, Sep. 1965; Sonneborn, T.M., (Tracy Morton), 1905-1981 (Box 67)
  - "Leloir Coenzymes, Cell Membranes and Protein Synthesis", Soodak, Morris (Box 67)
  - Sequence Complementarity of T2-DNA and T2-Specific RNA, 1961; Hall, Benjamin D.; Spiegelman, Sol (Box 67)
  - [With Honesty--America Must Face Reality], 27 Sep. 1966; Spock, Benjamin (Box 67)
  - Circular Mapping Functions for T4, n.d.; Stahl, Franklin W.; Steinberg, Charles Myron (Box 67)
  - The Effects of the Decay of Incorporated Radioactive Phosphorus on the Genome of Bacteriophage T4, n.d.; Stahl, Franklin W. (Box 67)
  - Some Circular Thoughts about Maps, n.d.; Stahl, Franklin W. (Box 67)
  - Virus-Induced Neoplasia--Outlook for the Future, Nov. 1959; Stanley, Wendell M. (Box 67)
  - Zur Herkunft des in der Transduktion Durch den Phagen P22, Starlinger, Peter (Box 67)
  - A Critical Test of a Current Theory of Genetic Recombination in Bacteriophage, Steinberg, Charles Myron (Box 67)
    See Ser.IV, Steinberg, Charles
  - Kinetics for a Three Locus Population, 3 Feb. 1958; Stahl, Franklin W.; Steinberg, Charles Myron (Box 67)
  - Some Theoretical Problems Arising in the Genetics of Bacteriophage, 1961; Steinberg, Charles Myron (Box 67)
  - The Theory of Formal Phage Genetics, n.d.; Stahl, Franklin W.; Steinberg, Charles Myron (Box 67)
  - The Chromosomal Site of the RNA Control (RC) Locus in Escherichia Coli, 1962; Alföldi, Lajos; Clowes, Royston C., 1921-; Stent, Gunther S. (Box 67)
  - Effects of Chloramphenicol and of Multiplicity of Infection on Induced Mutation in Bacteriophage T4, Fermi, Giulio; Stent, Gunther S. (Box 67)
  - Genetic and Physiological Effects of the Decay of Incorporated Radioactive Phosphorus in Bacterial Viruses and Bacteria, Stent, Gunther S. (Box 67)
  - Inactivation of Bacteriophages by Decay of Incorporated Radioactive Phosphorus, [1954]; Fuerst, Clarence R.; Stent, Gunther S. (Box 67)
  - Genetic Transduction in Bacteria, 1953; Stocker, B.A.D. (Box 68)
  - Lysogenic Conversion by the A Phages of Salmonella Typhimurium, n.d.; Stocker, B.A.D. (Box 68)
  - Chromosome Structure in Phage T4.III. Terminal Redundancy and Length Determination, [1966]; Emrich, Joyce; Stahl, Mary Morgan; Streisinger, George (Box 68)
  - The Direction of Translation of the Lysozyme Gene of Bacteriophage T4 Relative to the Linkage Map, n.d.; Emrich, Joyce; Stahl, Mary Morgan; Streisinger, George (Box 68)
  - A Frame Shift Mutation Resulting in the Deletion of Two Base Pairs in the Lysozyme Gene of Phage T4, n.d.; Akaboshi, E.; Inouye, Masayori; Streisinger, George (Box 68)
  - Frame Shift Mutations and the Genetic Code, 1966; Emrich, Joyce; Okada, Yoshimi; Streisinger, George (Box 68)
  - Frame-Shift Mutations and the Genetic Code. I. Analysis of the Lysozyme of the Double-Mutant Strain T4 eJ42eJ44, Okada, Y.; Streisinger, George; Terzaghi, E. (Box 68)
  - Frame-Shift Mutations and the Genetic Code. II. Analysis of the Lysozyme of the Double-Mutant Strain T4 eJ17eJ44, Emrich, Joyce; Okada, Y.; Streisinger, George; Terzaghi, E. (Box 68)
  - The Gross Structure of the Genome of Phage T4. I. The Circularity of the Linkage Map, n.d.; Denhardt, Georgetta Harrar; Edgar, Robert S.; Streisinger, George (Box 68)
  - The Gross Structure of the Genome of Phage T4. II. The Frequency of Terminal-Redundancy-Heterozygotes in the Presence of Fluorodeoxyuridine, Lanford, Henry; Streisinger, George; Séchaud, Janine (Box 68)
  - The Gross Structure of the Genome of Phage T4. II. The Frequency of Terminal-Redundancy-Heterozygotes in Genomes Containing Deletions, Emrich, Joyce; Stahl, Mary Morgan; Streisinger, George (Box 68)
  - Inheritance and Phenotypic Expression of Type Difference Characters in Bacteriophage, 1954; Streisinger, George (Box 68)
  - The Mechanism of 5 Bromouracil Mutagenesis in the Bacteriophage T4, n.d.; Stahl, Franklin W.; Streisinger, George; Terzaghi, Betty E. (Box 68)
  - Phage Genetics, 1954; Streisinger, George (Box 68)
  - On the Mechanism of Spontaneous Reversion and Genetic Recombination in Bacteriophage T4, Strigini, P. (Box 68)
  - Studies on sRNA Coded by Herpes Virus, n.d.; Shepherd, Wilma M.; Subak-Sharpe, H. (Box 68)
  - On the Genetic Basis of Variation and Heterogeneity of DNA Base Composition, Sueoka, Noboru (Box 68)
  - Some Genetic and Evolutionary Considerations on the Base Composition of Deoxyribonucleic Acids, Sueoka, Noboru (Box 68)
  - A Specific Modification of Leucyl-sRNA of Escherichia Coli After Phage T2 Infection, 1964; Kanosueoka, Tamiko; Sueoka, Noboru (Box 68)
  - Synchronous and Dichotomous Replication of the Bacillus Subtilis Chromosome During Spore Germination, 1964; Oishi, Michio; Sueoka, Noboru; Yoshikawa, Hiroshi (Box 68)
  - Mutations of Col E1 Plasmid That Affect Colicin Activity, n.d.; Suit, Joan L. (Box 68)
  - Interaction of Bacteriophage Lambda Repressor with Non-Operator DNA Containing Single Strand Gaps, Baluch, John; Calame, Kathryn; Resnick, James; Sussman, Raquel (Box 68)
  - [Course Materials], n.d.; Sussman (Box 68)